printcountry.com 2016-11-03

# Privacy Policy - Printer Ink Cartridges from PrintCountry

## Privacy Policy

Your privacy and the privacy of all registered users of **PrintCountry** is important to us. Accordingly, we have adopted the following privacy policy.

Our policy is based on the principles of notice, choice, access and security in the collection and use of all information regarding our users and their activities at our site. Please review this policy each time you use the site as it is subject to change at any time by **PrintCountry** without notice to you.

**Notice**

This policy tells you among other things what information we gather from you, how we may use or disclose that information, and our efforts to protect it.

**Types of Information Collected**

In connection with your use of our site, we ask for and may collect a variety of information from and about you in different ways. For example, when you purchase an item from our site, we may ask for and store your information including, but not limited to, your name and/or your business' name, address, email address, billing, shipping, payment information and other identifying contact data. When you use our printer driver tool, we confirm your email address and send you the link for the selected printer driver (if available) along with recommended products. This collected email will only be used and protected by GBSS, Inc. (parent company of PrintCountry.com), and will not be sold to another company.

**Use of Cookies**

Our site makes use of cookies when a visitor's Internet browser is set up to accept them. Cookies are small data files that our web site sends to your browser for storage on your computer's hard drive. We use cookies to identify members, track activity at our site, and better serve your needs and interests. Non-Personally Identifiable Information is collected by FetchBack for the purpose of online Retargeting. This information is used strictly for reporting purposes and is not tied to personal information. You are free to delete all cookies on your browser, or to have your browser notify you when a cookie is set. You can view FetchBack's Privacy Policy at http://www.fetchback.com/privacy.html

**Use of Information**

We use your personal identifying information to identify you as a user of the site and to assist and speed the completion of transactions on the site. We may use your email address to contact you directly regarding services or products that we believe may be of interest to you. We may also associate your personal identifying information with information we collect about your preferences and activities at the site, such as the particular pages you request at the site and purchases or other transactions you effect through the site. We may vary the content you receive in future visits to the site based on your preferences and activities. When you use our printer driver tool, we confirm your email address and send you the link for the selected printer driver (if available) along with recommended products. This collected email will only be used and protected by GBSS, Inc. (parent company of PrintCountry.com), and will not be sold to another company.

We may combine your personal identifying information, and information about your preferences and activities, with those of all or a particular group of our users to prepare collective profiles of our users and their activities. For example, we may track the number of our users who view certain pages or use certain features or we may compile the total dollar amount of sales conducted through our site in a particular geographic region. Such information, and other information we derive from individual users' information, allows us to continue to grow and provide you and fellow users with more accurate marketing and advertising of our Web site.

**Disclosure of Information**

If you provide us permission to do so, we may provide your personal identifying information, and information about your activities and preferences, to other companies wishing to contact you about products or services, but only to those that we believe impose reasonable safeguards on the privacy of your information. We may provide other companies with collective profiles of our user groups and their activities and preferences. Such collective profiles may also be disclosed in describing our site and services to prospective partners, advertisers and other third parties, and for other lawful purposes.

Additionally, with your approval, your personal, order and payment information may be shared with other companies.

Finally, we may disclose information to fulfill certain legal and regulatory requirements or if we believe, in good faith, that such disclosure is legally required or necessary to protect others' rights or to prevent harm.

**Analytics**

We use 3rd party statistics apps such as Google Analytics to analyze site traffic. This report includes but not limited to most visited pages, visitor behaviour and demographics. This data is anonymous, and visitors are not indentifiable in any way. If you choose not be included in these statistical data, we recommend [Google Analytics' opt-outs for the web (browser plugin)](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/) for the duration of your visit.
